I see a bank company stop started with
the counter opened in the green with a
profit of 1 point 51 percent at rupees
357 on the NSE
despite the market running over zero
point 70 percent ICICI Bank on Friday
sealed it has divested three point
ninety six percent stake in its general
insurance arm for nearly rupees two
thousand two hundred and fifty per hood
earlier on May 9th while announcing its
result for the March quarter ICICI Bank
had stated that it would look at further
straightening the balance sheet of
opportunities arises in line with this
intent and pursuant to an approval
granted by the board
the bank has today divested a team like
equity shares of face value rupees ten
each of ICICI Lombard general insurance
company representing three point ninety
six percent of equity share capital at
march 31st on the stock exchange for an
approximate total considerations of
rupees twenty two point fifty billion
ICICI Bank said following the beam the
bank's shareholding in icsea Hobart
general insurance company has fallen to
51.9% the private lender held fifty five
point eight three six percent stake in
the general insurance company as of
March 31st BAC data suggests and finally
to avoid huge losses in the stock market
flitting charas prick stop-loss and
thanks for your confidence